

Mr. Chems Eddine Senoussi

Software Developer Graphic designer

October 1st, 1995



Biskra, Algeria



Algerian



+213 699 65 32 91



https://chemsedd.github.io



chemsedd@outlook.fr (G



linkedin.com/in/chemsedd in



github.com/chemsedd



Languages

Arabic native **English** fluent French fluent

Hobbies

Video games Coding for fun **Swimming Documentaries** Movies

ABOUT ME

am Chems Eddine Senoussi, I'm a graduate with master's degree in Artificial Intelligence from Biskra University. My ineterests range from Machine/Deep Learning to all kinds of software development (web, desktop and mobile). I always try to learn new things, help people and contribute to projects, I aim to experience new things with new technologies. My goal is to have an impact on the computer science field and to contribute to the developement of technology.

EDUCATION

2020 - Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence - Computer Science

University of Mohamed Khider, Biskra, Algeria.

2018 - Bachelor degree in Computer Science

University of Mohamed Khider, Biskra, Algeria.

2014 - Baccalaureate degree in experimental sciences

Mekki Meni High School, Biskra, Algeria.

EXPERIENCES

(2020) Frontend Developer at Dimalab

I'm working with **Dimalab** agency as a frontend developer. We provide web solutions such as Storage and Queue Management Systems for companies and enterprises.

(2018 - 2020) Biskra Computer Science Club

I was the president of the university scientific club (BCSC). We organized different activities: programming workshops, conferences, competitions, etc. We hosted the 1st edition of Algerian Collegiate Programming Contest 2018 (ALCPC) in Algeria.

(2017 - Present) Graphic Designer

I've been working as a graphic designer since 2017, i do almost all kind of designs, vector graphics, posters, logos, banners, social media posts, business cards, etc. I use Adobe illustrator, Adobe Photoshop and Adobe XD.

(2010 - Present) Computers installation and repair

I repair computers and laptops (hardware and software), I've been doing this as a freelance service for years. I dealt with different issues and software problems.

SKILLS

Algorithm (data structures, problem solving) Python	OS (Windows, Linux) LaTEX
(numpy, pandas, tensorflow) Java (ODD JaveFV Patabases)	Raspberry Pi Arduino
(OOP, JavaFX, Databases) C (Pointers, socket, files)	Adobe illustrator
Web dev (Vue.js, Django)	Adobe Photoshop
IDEs / Editors (Pycharm, VS Code, VIm)	Adobe XD —

Personal Projects

(2017) Crowd Simulation using PSO algorithm

Realising a 3D simulation with Unity, of crowds moving toward a target while avoiding obstacles with Particle Swarm Optimization algorithm.

(2020) Smart Green

Data analytics system for monitoring Smart Farming, Built using Python (tensorflow, keras, pandas) and Django.